Finding Aid for the Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Annotated Scores, 1828-1993
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Annotated scores 1762-1993, I.; Folder 001-Folder 607
  - Eliasson, Anders, 1947- Disegno per pianoforte, 1985, 1 score (21 pages); Print Reimers Instrumentation: For solo piano Contains performance markings. Signed by Mikhashoff, Stockholm October 25, 1985. (Box 08, Folder 0150)
  - Erkel, Ferenc Bank Ban. Melinda Ariaja, 1955, 1 score (7 pages); Print (photocopy) Zenemukiado Vallalat Instrumentation: For soprano and piano Some phonetic pronunciations for the text. (Box 08, Folder 0151)
  - Etkin, Mariano Arenas para piano, 1988, 2 scores (7 pages each); Holograph (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano Contains performance markings. Found in folder marked Argentina and Uruguay Piano Music. One copy is enlarged format. Dedicated to the memory of Morton Feldman. (Box 08, Folder 0152)
  - Evangelisti, Franco Proiezioni sonore [1955/56: strutture per piano solo], 1961, 1 score (2 pages); Manuscript (photocopy) Edition Tonos Instrumentation: For solo piano Contains small number of performance markings. Poor quality photocopy. (Box 08, Folder 0153)
  - Falla, Manuel de, 1876-1946 Fantasia Baetica for piano, 1922, 1 score (25 pages); Print J. and W. Chester Instrumentation: For solo piano Contains performance markings. Signed by Mikhashoff. (Box 08, Folder 0154)
  - Falla, Manuel de, 1876-1946 Seven Spanish folk songs - Siete Canciones populares espanolas, 1949, 1 score (32 pages); Print Associated Music Instrumentation: For solo piano Contains performance markings. Signed by Mikhashoff. (Box 08, Folder 0155)
  - Farwell, Arthur, 1872-1952 Sonata for violoncello and piano: op. 116, 1975, 1 score (40 pages); Manuscript (Ozalid reproduction) Instrumentation: For violoncello and piano Contains performance markings. Signed by Mikhashoff. (Box 08, Folder 0156)
  - Felder, David Coleccion Nocturna, 1983, 1 score (23 pages); 36 cm.; Print (Photocopy) Wesleyan Music Instrumentation: For B flat clarinet/bass clarinet, piano, and four-channel tape Contains extensive performance markings. (Box 08, Folder 0157)
  - Felder, David Coleccion Nocturna, 1983, 2 scores (23 pages each); 28 cm.; Print (Photocopy) Wesleyan Music Instrumentation: For B flat clarinet/bass clarinet, piano, and four-channel tape Both scores contain performance markings. (Box 08, Folder 0158)
  - Felder, David Coleccion Nocturna, 1984 (score), 1986 (part), 1 score (34 pages); 44 cm. and 1 part (24 pages); Holograph score (photocopy); Manuscript piano part (Ozalid reproduction) Wesleyan Music Instrumentation: For solo B flat/bass clarinet, solo piano, orchestra, and four-channel tape Score marked with some questions; part contains small number of performance markings. Imprint on part is Wesleyan Music. (Box 08, Folder 0159)
  - Felder, David Passageways II, 1993, 1 part (8 pages); Print (photocopy) T. Presser Instrumentation: For flute/piccolo, trombone, percussion, electronic piano, piano, and violoncello Piano II part with small number of performance markings. (Box 08, Folder 0160)
  - Felder, David Rocket summer, 1984, 1 score (6 pages); Print (photocopy) T. Presser Instrumentation: For solo piano Contains changes and performance markings. (Box 08, Folder 0161)
  - Feldman, Morton, 1926-1987 Extensions III, 1962, 1 score (4 pages); Print (Reproduction of holograph, photocopy) Peters Instrumentation: For solo piano Contains small number of performance markings. (Box 08, Folder 0162)
  - Feldman, Morton, 1926-1987 For Frank O'Hara, 1973, 1 score (11 pages); Holograph (Ozalid reproduction) Instrumentation: For flute, clarinet, percussion, piano, violin, and violoncello Extensively marked for performance. (Box 08, Folder 0163)
  - Feldman, Morton, 1926-1987 For Philip Guston, 1984, 1 score (102 pages); Print (Ozalid reproduction of holograph) Universal Edition Instrumentation: For flute, percussion, and piano/celeste Extensively marked for performance. (Box 08, Folder 0164)
  - Feldman, Morton, 1926-1987 Intermission V, 1962, 2 scores (3 pages each); Print (Reproduction of holograph) Peters Instrumentation: For solo piano Print copy has only one marking; photocopy marked in several places. Signed by Mikhashoff. (Box 08, Folder 0165)
  - Feldman, Morton, 1926-1987 Piano piece (to Philip Guston), 1979, 1 score (2 pages); Holograph (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano Contains small number of markings. (Box 08, Folder 0166)
  - Feldman, Morton, 1926-1987 Piano piece 1952, 1962, 1 score (2 pages); Holograph (Reproduction of holograph) C. F. Peters Instrumentation: For solo piano Duration marked in caption; no other markings. (Box 08, Folder 0167)
  - Feldman, Morton, 1926-1987 Piano piece 1956 A, 1961, 1 score (2 pages); Print (Reproduction of holograph (photocopy)) Peters Instrumentation: For solo piano Duration marked in caption; contains small number of other markings. (Box 08, Folder 0168)
  - Feldman, Morton, 1926-1987 Piano piece 1956 A, 1961, 1 score (2 pages); Holograph (reproduction) Peters Instrumentation: For solo piano Duration marked in caption; other markings photocopied from preceding copy. (Box 08, Folder 0169)
  - Feldman, Morton, 1926-1987 Piano piece 1956 B, 1962, 1 score (2 pages); Print (Reproduction of holograph (photocopy)) [Peters] Instrumentation: For solo piano Duration marked in caption; also contains performance markings. (Box 08, Folder 0170)
  - Feldman, Morton, 1926-1987 Piano piece 1956 B, 1962, 1 score (2 pages); Print (Reproduction of holograph (photocopy)) [Peters] Instrumentation: For solo piano Duration marked in caption; other markings photocopied from preceding copy. (Box 08, Folder 0171)
  - Feldman, Morton, 1926-1987 Piano, 1977, 1 score (14 pages); Holograph (Reproduction) Universal Edition Instrumentation: For solo piano Extensive performance markings that reflect Mikhashoff's rehearsals with Feldman. Signed by Mikhashoff. (Box 09, Folder 0172)
  - Fennelly, Brian Empirical Rag: version for piano, 1978, 1 score (8 pages); Holograph (Photocopy) Distributed by American Composers Alliance Instrumentation: For solo piano Emendations marked in red. (Box 09, Folder 0173)
  - Fennimore, Joseph Folder of five works, undated, 5 scores; Holograph (Original and photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano and voice and piano Scores contain emendations. (Box 09, Folder 0174)
    Cleaning the attic (song) -- Beware the web you cannot see (Song) -- Songs and dances (for Johnnie) Books I and II (solo piano) -- Untitled set of variations for solo piano.
  - Fennimore, Joseph Waltzes, undated, 1 score (25 pages); Holograph (Ozalid reproduction) Instrumentation: For solo piano Score is unmarked. A set of nine waltzes, the first of which is four waltzes in one, dedicated to Ronald McKay (Mikhashoff). Accompanied by an earlier ink and pencil manuscript version of the waltzes for McKay (5 leaves). (Box 09, Folder 0175)
  - Franchetti, Arnold, 1906-1993 Solletti d'Ebe per violoncello e pianoforte, 1971, 1 score (10 pages); Holograph (Ozalid reproduction) Instrumentation: For violoncello and piano Contains performance markings. Dedicated to Paolo Olefsky. (Box 09, Folder 0176)
  - Finney, Ross Lee, 1906-1997 2 acts for 3 players, 1975, 1 part (8 pages); Print Peters (Henmar) Instrumentation: For clarinet, percussion, and piano Percussion part marked for performance. (Box 09, Folder 0177)
  - Finney, Ross Lee, 1906-1997 24 piano inventions, 1971, 1 score (23 pages); Print Peters Instrumentation: For solo piano Number 9 contains a few slight markings. (Box 09, Folder 0178)
  - Finney, Ross Lee, 1906-1997 Lost calf whale, 1980, 1 score (3 pages); Print (Reproduction of manuscript) Henmar Instrumentation: For solo piano Contains some performance instructions. (Box 09, Folder 0179)
  - Finney, Ross Lee, 1906-1997 Nostalgic waltzes, 1953, 1 score (16 pages); Print (photocopy) Mercury (Presser) Instrumentation: For solo piano Contains only a few markings. (Box 09, Folder 0180)
  - Finney, Ross Lee, 1906-1997 Waltz for piano (1977), 1978, 1 score (4 pages); Print (photocopy) Peters Instrumentation: For solo piano Two-sided copy: one side contains small number of fingerings; second side marked with instrumentation for an arrangement. (Box 09, Folder 0181)
  - Finney, Ross Lee, 1906-1997 Youth's companion: five short pieces for piano, 1981, 1 score (14 pages); Print Peters Instrumentation: For solo piano Contains performance markings. Signed by Mikhashoff. (Box 09, Folder 0182)
  - Finnissy, Michael Banumbirr, 1982, 1 score (28 pages); Holograph (reproduction) United Music Instrumentation: For flute, clarinet, violin, violoncello, and piano Contains a few markings on first page of score. (Box 09, Folder 0183)
  - Flagello, Nicolas Credendum: for violin and orchestra, 1985, 1 score (57 pages); Holograph (photocopy) Instrumentation: For violin and orchestra Contains small number of changes to the score. "Composed 1973, orchestrated 1985"--Title page. Budget figures written on verso of last page. (Box 09, Folder 0184)
  - Flanagan, William, 1923-1969 Sonata for piano, 1957, 1 score (13 pages); Print Peer International Instrumentation: For solo piano Contains performance markings. (Box 09, Folder 0185)
  - Foss, Lukas, 1922-2009 Solo for piano, 1982, 1 score (32 pages); Print Pembroke Music Instrumentation: For solo piano Contains performance markings and changes. Cover inscribed by composer, to Mikhashoff. Performance dates listed on verso of cover. Work commissioned by Mikhashoff. (Box 09, Folder 0186)
  - Foss, Lukas, 1922-2009 Three airs for Frank O'Hara's Angel, 1972, 1 score (20 pages); Holograph (photocopy) Instrumentation: For soprano, countertenor, violoncello or viola, and cembalo/piano Contains performance markings. (Box 09, Folder 0187)
  - Weill, Kurt, 1900-1950 Sieben Stücke nach der Dreigroschenoper, 1930, 1 score (24 pages) and 1 part (11 pages); Print Universal Edition Instrumentation: For violin and piano Violin part marked for performance; score is not marked. Arranged by Stefan Frenkel. Additional name: Frenkel, Stefan, 1902-1979 (Box 09, Folder 0188)
  - Frounberg, Ivar, 1950- Messages from the mermaid coast: small waves and a ship along the coast in the mist (short version), undated, 1 score (3 pages); Holograph (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano Marked with durations of sections. Dedicated to Mikhashoff. (Box 09, Folder 0189)
  - Galán, Carlos, 1963- Poema de Soledades, 1989, 1 score (16 pages); Holograph (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano Contains some performance markings. Commissioned by Mikhashoff. (Box 09, Folder 0190)
  - Gandini, Gerardo, 1936- Eusebius, 1984, 1 score (4 pages); Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano Contains small number of markings. (Box 09, Folder 0191)
  - Gena, Peter McKinley, 1983, 1 score (11 pages); Holograph (photocopy) Instrumentation: For violin, piano, and percussion Marked for performance. Accompanied by typescript note (1 leaf) from composer with some performance instructions. (Box 09, Folder 0192)
  - Gerhard, Roberto, 1896-1970 Concerto for harpsichord, string orchestra and percussion, 1959, 1 score (22 pages); Print (photocopy) Mills Music Instrumentation: For harpsichord, string orchestra, and percussion Marked for performance. (Box 09, Folder 0193)
  - Germani, Ferruccio, 1950- Via Crucis, undated, 2 scores (15 pages each); Holograph (photocopy) Instrumentation: For two pianos Only one copy has very small number of markings. Accompanied by two copies of typescript (3 leaves) performance instructions. (Box 09, Folder 0194)
  - Gershwin, George, 1898-1937 Concerto in f for piano and orchestra, 1927, 1 score (67 pages); Print New World Music Instrumentation: For piano and orchestra; arranged for 2 pianos, 4 hands Brackets for first piano highlighted in third movement. Signed by Mikhashoff. (Box 09, Folder 0195)
  - Gershwin, George, 1898-1937 Impromptu in two keys, 1973, 1 score (2 pages); Print (photocopy) New World Instrumentation: For solo piano Contains some fingerings. (Box 09, Folder 0196)
  - Giacobbe, Juan Francisco Siete Imagenes de Tango: Proemio and recitativo, undated, 1 score (6 pages); Holograph (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano Some passages are circled. Found in folder marked Argentina and Uruguay Piano Music. (Box 09, Folder 0197)
  - Ginastera, Alberto, 1916-1983 Twelve American preludes: volume I, 1946, 1 score (13 pages); Print Carl Fischer Instrumentation: For solo piano Contains some performance markings. Includes number 12 from second volume. (Box 09, Folder 0198)
  - Ginastera, Alberto, 1916-1983 Twelve American preludes: volume II, 1946, 2 scores (13 pages each); Print Carl Fischer Instrumentation: For solo piano One copy without cover contains some performance markings. One copy signed by Mikhashoff with no other markings. (Box 09, Folder 0199)
  - Glass, Philip Einstein on the beach: an opera in four acts, undated, 2 scores (pages 1-150 and pages 151-222); Manuscript (photocopy) Theodore Presser Instrumentation: For instrumental ensemble, chorus, and vocal soloists (spoken and sung) The very few markings include those on pages 53-55. Acts 1-3, bound together. Act 4, loose. Additional name: Wilson, Robert, 1941- (Box 10, Folder 0200)
  - Glass, Philip Glassworks. Opening, 1984, 1 score (2 pages); Print Dunvagen (T. Presser) Instrumentation: For solo piano Very few markings. (Box 10, Folder 0201)
  - Glass, Philip Modern love waltz, undated, parts (4 pages); Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: Originally for solo piano, these parts seem to be for the instrumental version Some annotations Parts for Trombone (or Violoncello or bassoon), Clarinet in A, and Clarinet in B-flat. There is an instrumental version arranged by Robert Moran but it isn't clear that these parts are for that arrangement. Additional name: Moran, Robert, 1937- (Box 10, Folder 0202)
  - Gleason, Harold, 1892-1980 Examples of music before 1400, 1945, 1 score (117 pages); Print Appleton-Century-Crofts Instrumentation: For various vocal and instrumental combinations The printed score itself contains very few markings. Signed by Mikhashoff; annotations and transcriptions throughout, many photocopies and additional notes and clippings from unidentified reference sources (Box 10, Folder 0203)
    In addition to the printed volume and photocopies pages, there are four ink manuscript scores, including transcriptions of Francesco Landini's Ballata, Adiu, adiu and his Ecco la primavera, the anonymous Una hija tenia el rey, and a contemporary setting for voice and piano of the text of Westron wynde, when wilt thou blow? This is possibly a Mikhashoff composition. It is dated January 1970.
  - Godowsky, Leopold, 1870-1938 Renaissance. Minuet, A minor, 1906, 1 score (11 pages); Print Schlesinger'sche Buch und Musikhandlung Instrumentation: For solo piano Includes annotations on score of Rameau's original version. Based on the Menuett in A minor by Jean-Philippe Rameau. Band 1 no. 3 of Renaissance, freie Bearbeitungen alter Meisterstücke. Additional name: Rameau, Jean-Philippe, 1683-1764 (Box 10, Folder 0204)
  - Goehr, Alexander, 1932- Nonomiya: for piano, op. 27, 1973, 1 score (13 pages); Print Schott Instrumentation: For solo piano Contains performance markings. Signed by Mikhashoff. (Box 10, Folder 0205)
  - Gordon, Michael, 1956- Thou Shalt! / Thou Shalt Not!, 1984, 1 score (34 pages); Manuscript (Reproduction) Instrumentation: For electric violin, electric viola, amplified bass, clarinet, percussion, electric guitar, and electric organ The only marking is a date on the title page. (Box 10, Folder 0206)
  - Granados, Enrique, 1867-1916 Album of Enrique Granados Masterpieces: 12 danzas españolas (Spanish dances): for piano solo, 1941, 1 score (66 pages); Print Edward B. Marks Music Instrumentation: For solo piano Contains one marking Signed and dated by Mikhashoff. Series: Contemporary masterpieces, album no. 4. (Box 10, Folder 0207)
  - Grant, Julian, 1960- Pond. Alligator song, 1991, 1 score (13 pages); Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano Heavily marked for performance and to create solo piano excerpt Signed by Mikhashoff. (Box 10, Folder 0208)
  - Grieg, Edvard, 1843-1907 Bergliot: op. 42 Klavierauszug, undated, 1 score (22 pages); Print Edition Peters Instrumentation: Originally for narrator and orchestra. This is the vocal score with orchestra reduced for piano Contains performance markings. Text in German and Norwegian by Bjørnstjerne Bjørnson. Additional name: Bjørnson, Bjørnstjerne, 1832-1910 (Box 10, Folder 0209)
  - Grieg, Edvard, 1843-1907 Grieg-Album: udvalgte kompositioner for piano. II. Bind, 1921, 1 score (29 pages); Print Wilhelm Hansen Instrumentation: For solo piano Contains only a small number of markings. (Box 10, Folder 0210)
  - Grieg, Edvard, 1843-1907 Lyrical pieces for the piano, op. 54, 1932, 1 score (20 pages); Print G. Schirmer Instrumentation: For solo piano Notturno, op. 54, no. 4 marked for performance. Pages 21-23 missing. (Box 10, Folder 0211)
  - Griffes, Charles Tomlinson, 1884-1920 Sonata for piano, 1921, 1 score (31 pages); Print G. Schirmer Instrumentation: For solo piano Contains performance markings. (Box 10, Folder 0212)
  - Gruenberg, Louis, 1884-1964 Daniel jazz: for voice and eight instruments, 1925, 1 score (60 pages); Print (photocopy) Universal Edition Instrumentation: For Clarinet, Trumpet, percussion, voice, violins, viola, violoncello, and piano Some places in the vocal part are highlighted. Text by Vachel Lindsay. Additional name: Lindsay, Vachel, 1879-1931 (Box 10, Folder 0213)
  - Guarnieri, Camargo, 1907-1993 Ponteios (preludios) para piano: 1 caderno (da 1 a 10), 1969, 1 score (28 pages); Print Ricordi Instrumentation: For solo piano Ponteio no. 7 has markings that might have been the beginning of an arrangement by Mikhashoff. Signed by Mikhashoff and dated July 25 1980. (Box 10, Folder 0214)
  - Guarnieri, Camargo, 1907-1993 Ponteios (preludios) para piano: 2 caderno (da 11 a 20), 1956, 1 score (24 pages); Print Ricordi Instrumentation: For solo piano Ponteio no. 17 has markings that might have been the beginning of an arrangement by Mikhashoff. Signed by Mikhashoff and dated July 25 1980. (Box 10, Folder 0215)
  - Guarnieri, Camargo, 1907-1993 Ponteios (preludios) para piano: 3 caderno (da 21 a 30), 1976, 1 score (24 pages); Print Musicalia Instrumentation: For solo piano Ponteio no. 24 has markings that might have been the beginning of an arrangement by Mikhashoff. (Box 10, Folder 0216)
  - Guarnieri, Camargo, 1907-1993 Ponteios (preludios) para piano: 4 caderno (da 31 a 40), 1959, 1 score (27 pages); Print Ricordi Instrumentation: For solo piano Ponteio no. 36 and no. 38 are marked "For vln & pf". Signed by Mikhashoff and dated July 25 1980. (Box 10, Folder 0217)
  - Guarnieri, Camargo, 1907-1993 Ponteios (preludios) para piano: 5 caderno (da 41 a 50), 1970, 1 score (29 pages); Print Ricordi Instrumentation: For solo piano Ponteio no. 45 marked "For orchestra (1958)"; Ponteio no. 46 marked "For string orchestra (1959)"; Ponteio no. 48 marked "For string quartet (1959)". Signed by Mikhashoff and dated July 26 1980. (Box 10, Folder 0218)
  - Haieff, Alexei, 1914-1994 Gifts and semblances for piano solo: Sirocco-porto ercole, 1954, 1 score (2 pages); Print (photocopy) Boosey & Hawkes Instrumentation: For solo piano The only markings are the title of the collective work and the composer's name. (Box 10, Folder 0219)
  - Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003 Double concerto for violin, violoncello, and Javanese gamelan: Stampede (2nd movement), undated, 1 score (15 pages) and 1 part (8 pages); Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For violin, violoncello, and Javanese gamelan Violoncello part marked for performance. Consists of score for 2nd movement, Stampede, and violoncello part. Title on cover of violoncello part: "Kendang - Stampede" (Box 10, Folder 0220)
  - Hartmann, Thomas de, 1885-1956 Two nocturnes: piano solo (op. 84), 1955, 1 score (22 pages); Print M. P. Belaieff Instrumentation: For solo piano Contains performance markings. (Box 10, Folder 0221)
  - Haubenstock-Ramati, Roman Klavierstücke (1), 1966, 1 score (16 pages); Print (photocopy) Universal Edition Instrumentation: For solo piano Piece 3 marked for performance. (Box 10, Folder 0222)
  - Hauer, Josef Matthias, 1883-1959 Etüden für Klavier: Heft I (op. 22.1), 1926, 1 score (4 pages); Print (photocopy) Universal Edition Instrumentation: For solo piano Contains a small number of markings. (Box 10, Folder 0223)
  - Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809 Sämtliche Klaviersonaten: Band 1a, 1966, 1 score (113 pages); Print Wiener Urtext Edition/B. Schott Instrumentation: For solo piano There are some performance markings on Sonata 10. (Box 11, Folder 0224)
  - Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809 Sonaten fur Klavier zu zwei Handen. Band II, 1937, 1 score (115 pages); Print C. F. Peters Instrumentation: For solo piano There are some performance markings on Sonata 12. (Box 11, Folder 0225)
  - Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809 Sonaten fur Klavier zu zwei Handen. Band IV, 1937, 1 score (99 pages); Print C. F. Peters Instrumentation: For solo piano There are just a few performance markings on Sonata 40. (Box 11, Folder 0226)
  - Hays, Sorrel, 1941- Sunday nights: for piano, 1977, 1 score (5 pages); Holograph (Ozalid reproduction) Instrumentation: For solo piano Contains only a few performance markings. Name stated as "Doris Hays" on title page. (Box 11, Folder 0227)
  - Hedstrøm, Åse, 1950- Signs and pictures: for piano (1988/89), 1989, 1 score (13pages); Holograph (Reproduction) Distributed by Norsk Musikkinformasion Instrumentation: For solo piano Contains performance markings, questions concerning pitches, and an alternate version of the first two measures on the title page verso. Commissioned by and dedicated to Mikhashoff. (Box 11, Folder 0228)
  - Hill, Jackson, 1941- Remembered landscape: for piano quartet, 1984, 1 score (28 pages); Manuscript (Reproduction) Instrumentation: For violin, viola, violoncello, and piano Contains a small number of performance markings. Signed by Mikhashoff. (Box 11, Folder 0229)
  - Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Diabelskie Skrzypce: for stringed instrument and piano, 1978-1980, 4 scores; Holograph (Reproduction) Instrumentation: For diabelskie skrzypce (devil's fiddle) and piano or harpsichord Three of the scores are marked as indicated in the note. Dedicated to France-Marie Uitti and Mikhashoff. Signed by Mikhashoff. (Box 11, Folder 0230)
    [A]. Photoreproduction of holograph. 13 taped leaves. On titlepage: First performance Middelburg, Holland, June 30, 1978. Piano/harpsichord part heavily marked with performance indications. [B]. Photoreproduction of holograph. 13 taped leaves. This copy has barlines and time signatures added to what was in place in copy [A]. Keyboard part marked "Harpsichord" and heavily marked for performance. [C]. Photoreproduction of holograph. 12 loose leaves with title page and sheet of instructions for performers. Barlines retained from copy [B] but time signatures changed to quarter note values from eighth notes (10/8 becomes 5/4). No annotations. [D]. Printed reproduction of holograph. 10 pages. Copyright 1980. The only markings are some keyboard fingerings on page 1.
  - Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Fantasy for three pianos, 1951, 1 score (71 pages); Print (Reproduction of manuscript) Instrumentation: For three pianos Marked for performance. Signed by Mikhashoff. Label on front cover: "Indian Sonata". (Box 11, Folder 0231)
  - Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Five Appalachian ballads for voice and keyboard, undated, 1 score (31 pages); Holograph (Photocopy) Instrumentation: For voice and piano Contains performance markings and some markings for pronunciations. (Box 11, Folder 0232)
    I. Lord Randal -- II. Barbara Allen -- III. The three ravens -- IV. The cruel mother -- V. The two sisters.